freecoinhunt.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Freecoin Hunt to Get Free token

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets forth the general rules of the collection, processing, and storage of our users’ personal information of Freecoin Hunt (the “Company”, “US” or “We”).

This Policy applies to all services provided by Freecoin Hunt, including Freecoin Hunt’s software applications and Freecoin Hunt’s website.

The personal data we may collect and purpose of collection

We may collect and process the following personal data in order to deliver our services and contents:

  * Email address
  * Social Media
  * Username
  * Avatar image
  * Reading history(Strictly on our Website/Apps only)
  * Interactions (e.g. Favorited projects)
  * F energy counts

We use the listed information to:

  * Provide, improve our services
  * Combat spam and forms of abuse
  * Better understand how people use our services

Tracking & Cookies

We use minimum Cookie or similar technology as follows for the convenience of our users:

Performance cookies: Typical built-in cookies to improve the performance of our Website(e.g. compatibility with the browser).

Preference cookies: This kind of cookies remembers your site preferences (e.g. language) and the logins.

You may block or delete the cookies in your browser settings.

GDPR Compliance

  * In compliance with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), all users subject to the GDPR have rights in relation to the personal data:
  * You have the right to be informed regarding what data does Freecoin Hunt collect, as you are reading this Policy.
  * You have the right to be provided with a copy of the data we collect from you upon request. Please do note that this may take up to 30 calendars days to complete.
  * You have the right to request us to correct any information about you that may be incomplete or inaccurate.
  * You have the right to request us to delete the information that we have about you.
  * You have the right to request us to suspend processing your personal data.
  * You have the right to be provided with a copy of the data we collect from you in common format upon request(e.g., to reuse the data for your own purpose). Please do note that this may take up to 40 calendars days to complete.
  * You have the right to object to us processing your personal data.
  * You have the right to be informed in relations to the profiling or any automated decision making.

Our Commitment To Privacy Protection

We treat our users’ privacy with the utmost respect and attention. We have designated staff regularly review the relevant regulation, rule, law changes to enforce the privacy protection. For requests or inquiries concerning user privacy, do not hesitate to contact us at support@freecoinhunt.com , our designated staff will respond to requests or inquiries within 48 hours.

Updates And Changes Of The Privacy Policy

Please keep in mind that we may update the Policy from time to time. If any significant changes to the Policy, all users will be notified by Email, in-App alerts and will be announced by Freecoin Hunt on its Website.

We strongly advise you to review the updated Policy upon notice to stay informed about the updates and changes.
